<?xml version="1.0"?>
<shkaran>

<BookSite>Books In Paradise</BookSite>
<StudentName studentNumber="991377695" studentProg="Computer System Technician Software-Engenering">karan sharma</StudentName>
<Books>		
		  <Book>
     		<Name Image="Davincicode.jpg">The Da Vinci Code</Name>
		    <Desc BookType="A Novel">This is mystery writing at its best: gripping, intelligent, and original. 
			A brilliant Harvard professor and a beautiful French cryptologist get mixed up with Opus Dei, 
			a deeply devout yet highly controversial Catholic sect</Desc>
			<AuthorName>Dan Brown</AuthorName>
			<PublisherName>Knopf Doubleday</PublisherName>
			<CurrentPrice>$24.74</CurrentPrice>
			
		</Book>
		
		  <Book>	
     		<Name Image = "TheShallows.jpg">The Shallows</Name>
		    <Desc Type = "Science| Nature">Is Google making us stupid?” 
			When Nicholas Carr posed that question, in a celebrated Atlantic Monthly cover story, 
			he tapped into a well of anxiety about how the Internet is changing us. 
			He also crystallized one of the most important debates of our time: As we enjoy 
			the Net’s bounties, are we sacrificing our ability to read and think deeply?   </Desc>
			<AuthorName>Nicholas Carr</AuthorName>
			<PublisherName> WW Norton</PublisherName>
			<CurrentPrice>$13.18 </CurrentPrice>
					</Book>
		
		 <Book>
	    	
     		<Name Image="HouseOfLeaves.jpg">House of Leaves</Name>
		    <Desc Type="Fiction | Literature | Horror">  Years ago, when House of Leaves was first being passed around, it was nothing more than a 
			badly bundled heap of paper, parts of which would occasionally surface on the Internet. No one could have anticipated the small but devoted 
			following this terrifying story would soon command. Starting with an odd assortment of marginalized youth -- musicians, tattoo artists, programmers, 
			strippers, environmentalists, and adrenaline junkies -- the book eventually made its way into the hands of older generations, who not only found
			themselves in those strangely arranged pages but also discovered a way back into the lives of their estranged children. </Desc>
			<AuthorName>Mark Z. Danielewski</AuthorName>
			<PublisherName> Knopf Doubledayi</PublisherName>
			<CurrentPrice>$17.30 </CurrentPrice>
			
		</Book>
		
		
		 <Book>
	    	
     		<Name Image="Introtoalgo.jpeg">Introduction to Algorithms</Name>
		    <Desc Type="Computer | Technology"> Some books on algorithms are rigorous but incomplete; others cover masses of material but lack rigor.
			Introduction to Algorithms uniquely combines rigor and comprehensiveness. The book covers a broad range of algorithms in depth, yet makes their
			design and analysis accessible to all levels of readers. Each chapter is relatively self-contained and can be used as a unit of study.
			The algorithms are described in English and in a pseudocode designed to be readable by anyone who has done a little programming.
			The explanations have been kept elementary without sacrificing depth of coverage or mathematical rigor. </Desc>
			<AuthorName>Thomas H. Cormen, Charles E. Leiserson, Ronald L. Rivest</AuthorName>
			<PublisherName> The MIT Press</PublisherName>
			<CurrentPrice>$103.35</CurrentPrice>

		</Book>
</Books>
</shkaran>